#### **CONTACTS**

#### +447442467108

oleksandrtkachenko202@gmail.com

<u>Telegram</u>

linkedin

<u>GitHub</u>

Ivybridge, Devon, England

#### **TECH SKILLS**

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- Parcel
- AJAX
- REST API

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Strategic thinking
- Quick learning skills
- · Ability to work efficiently both
- individually and in a team

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

# **OLEKSANDR TKACHENKO**

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **SUMMARY**

I am Full Stack Developerwith a solid understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. I have experience working on team projects and specialize in creating visually appealing and user-friendly web applications, while also writing efficient code in JavaScript. My passion for innovation motivates me to constantly expand my skillset and explore new technologies. I am a quick learner with strong attention to detail, and I am excited to join a team where I can continue to develop both personally and professionally and make meaningful contributions to project success.

# PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

• Bookshelf. GitHub [HTML, SASS, JS, REST API, AJAX, Parcel]

The website is a search platform for books based on the use of API services and JavaScript libraries. Role: developer.

Phopebook, GitHub [React, React hooks, JSX]

Phone Book is an application that saves contacts in local storage and sorts them based on entered characters.

• <u>Ice-cream</u>, <u>GitHub</u> [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel]

Ice-company website with responsive layout, burger menu, modal window, animations, gallery with a JS library and attractive design. Role: developer.

• Webstudio, GitHub [HTML, CSS]

Webstudio website with a Multiple-page Application architecture. Role: developer.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### web-developer.in.ua

April 2023-present. Junior Frontend Developer (volunteer). Responsibilities:

• responsible for the Motivation section.

### Chernihiv Scientific and Research Expert-Criminalistic Center of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine.

2016-2022. Forensic Expert.

Responsibilities:

- Carrying out inspection and analysis of vehicles for changes in license plates.
- Preparing and presenting reports and documents related to the conducted expertise.

Achievements: conducted practical training for interns who successfully found employment after completing their internship.

# Scientific and Research Expert-Criminalistic Center of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine in Kyiv region.

2015-2016. Forensic Expert.

Responsibilities:

- Investigation of the crime scene, search for evidence of the crime
- Conducting trace, ballistic, and fingerprint examinations.

Achievements: helped to solve a number of crimes.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **IT School GoIT**

2022 - 2023

Fullstack Developer

#### **Chernihiv Polytechnic National University**

2017 - 2018

Master's degree. Motor vehicle transport.

# Academy of Business and Entrepreneurship

2005 - 2008

Master's degree. Enterprise economy.